Guide to the Fredericka Martin Papers ALBA.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: General Subject Files, 1937-1990
  - Spain: Andalucia, 1978-1982 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Spain: Arts and Culture: Clippings: Folder 1, 1966-1979 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Spain: Arts and Culture: Clippings: Folder 2, 1966-1979 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Spain: Arts and Culture: Clippings: Folder 3, 1966-1979 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Spain: Arts and Culture: Clippings, 1980-1982 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Spain: Barcelona: Clippings, undated, 1971-1973 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Spain: Calvo Sotelo, Rafael: Clippings, 1974-1982 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Spain: Camacho, Marcelino: Clippings, 1970-1976 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Spain: Carillo, Santiago, 1971-1978 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Spain: Carlists: Clippings, 1968-1975 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Spain: Carrero Blanco, Luis: Clippings, 1973-1976 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Spain: Censorship: Clippings, 1968-1982 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Spain: Constitution: Clippings, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Spain: European Relations, 1975-1981 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Spain: Falange: Clippings, 1969-1979 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Spain: Forest, Eva: Clippings, undated, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Spain: Fraga Iribarne, Manuel: Clippings, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Spain: Guidebooks and Souvenirs, undated, 1947-1986 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Spain: Juan Carlos: Clippings, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Spain: Juan Carlos: Clippings, 1970-1973 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Spain: Juan Carlos: Clippings, 1974-1976 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Spain: Juan Carlos: Clippings, 1976- 1980 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Spain: Juan Carlos Coronation: Clippings, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Spain: Labor: Clippings, 1969-1973 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Spain: Lister, Enrique: Clippings, 1937, 1966-1981 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Spain: Martinez Bordiu Franco, Maria del Carmen: Clippings, 1972-1975 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Spain: Monarchy: Notes and Clippings, 1968-1976 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Spain: National Geographic Magazine devoted to Spanish Culture, Mar 1929 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Spain: Opus Dei: Clippings, 1969-1977 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Spain: Parliament: Clippings, 1969-1980 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Spain: Political Prisoners, undated, 1940-1979 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Spain: Politics: Clippings, undated (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Spain: Politics: Clippings, 1939-1958 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Spain: Politics: Clippings, 1960-1964 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Spain: Politics: Clippings, 1967-1968 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Spain: Politics: Clippings, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Spain: Politics: Clippings, 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Spain: Politics: Clippings (Folder 1), 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Spain: Politics: Clippings (Folder 2), 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Spain: Politics: Clippings, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Spain: Politics: Clippings (Folder 1), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Spain: Politics: Clippings (Folder 2), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Spain: Politics: Clippings (Folder 3), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Spain: Politics: Clippings (Folder 1), 1976 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Spain: Politics: Clippings (Folder 2), 1976 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Spain: Politics: Clippings (Folder 1), 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Spain: Politics: Clippings (Folder 2), 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Spain: Politics: Clippings, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Spain: Politics: Clippings (Folder 1), 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Spain: Politics: Clippings (Folder 2), 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Spain: Politics: Clippings, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Spain: Politics: Clippings, 1983-1987 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Spain: Relations with Mexico: Clippings, undated, 1968-1974 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Spain: Relations with Mexico: Clippings, 1975-1976 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Spain: Relations with Mexico: Clippings, 1977-1979 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Spain: Relations with Mexico: Clippings, 1980-1982 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Spain: Relations with Mexico: Portillo's Visit to Spain: Clippings, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Spain: Relations with Mexico: Portillo's Visit to Spain: Clippings, 1978-1981 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Spain: Relations with Soviet Union: Clippings, 1968-1979 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Spain: Religion, undated, 1938-1939, 1968-1982 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Spain: Socialist Party (PSOE): Clippings, 1971-1982 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Spain: Suarez, Adolfo: Clippings, 1977-1982 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Spain: Travel Maps, undated (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Spain: Travel Postcards, Tickets and Souvenirs, undated, 1947 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Spain: Union Centro Democratico: Clippings, 1978-1982 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Spain: U.S. Foreign Relations, 1936-1939, 1945-1977 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Spain: U.S. Foreign Relations: Clippings, 1966-1981 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Spain: Women's Issues: Clippings, 1972-1979 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Spanish Civil War: Bibliographic Sources, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Spanish Civil War: Bibliographies: García Durán, Juan, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Spanish Civil War: Book Reviews, undated, 1939-1979 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Spanish Civil War: Child Welfare, undated, 1938 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Spanish Civil War: Clippings, 1936-1939 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Spanish Civil War: Clippings, undated, 1942-1985 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Spanish Civil War: Graves, undated, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Spanish Civil War: International Brigade Directive on Rank, 1937 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Spanish Civil War: Prisoners and Concentration Camps, undated, 1938-1939, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Spanish Civil War: Research Repositories, undated, 1970-1975 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Spanish Communist Party: Clippings, 1968-1982 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Spanish Communist Party Report on China, undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Spanish Cuisine, undated (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Spanish Refugee Aid, Inc. (includes Nancy Macdonald correspondence with FM), 1970-1982 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Spanish Writers: Clippings, 1935, 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Thomas, Norman, undated, 1971-1977 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Trotsky, Leon, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - U.S. Committee for a Democratic Spain, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - United American Spanish Aid Committee, 1940-1941 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Vallejo, César: Clippings, undated, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Western Europese Conferentie Voor Spanje, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Tarazona: Training Camp, 1938, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Veterans: Abraham Lincoln Brigade: Notes and Clippings, undated, 1938-1976 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Veterans: Abraham Lincoln Brigade Veterans Living in Mexico, undated, 1940, 1970-1972 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Veterans: Cleveland Volunteers, undated (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Veterans: Pensions for Disabled Republican Soldiers, undated, 1940, 1973-1977 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Veterans: Re-entry Permits for Resident Aliens: Correspondence (photocopies), 1939 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Veterans: Wisconsin Volunteers, undated, 1970-1980 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade (VALB): Association with Medical Volunteers, undated, 1979-1983 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade (VALB): Barcelona Movement, undated, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade (VALB): Correspondence, Roberts, Leaflets, undated, 1948-1988 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade (VALB): 40th Anniversary Program Honoring Women, undated, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade (VALB): 50th Anniversary Celebration, 1985-1987 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade (VALB): Florida Post, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade (VALB): FM Critiques of, undated (Box 29, Folder 37A)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade (VALB): Historical Commission, undated, 1967-1983 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade (VALB): International Brigades Archive (Moscow) Controversy: Correspondence, undated, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade (VALB): Name (FM comments on "Brigade" vs. "Battalion" controversy), undated (Box 29, Folder 39A)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade (VALB): Subversive Activities Control Board (SACB), undated, 1947-1980 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade (VALB): Veterans Recognition Campaign, undated, 1971, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade (VALB): West Coast (including FM dispute with), undated, 1962-1984 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade (VALB): Western Hemisphere Meeting: Correspondence and Notes, undated, 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade (VALB) Questionnaire for Wounded Vets: Correspondence Requesting Participation, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade (VALB) Questionnaire for Wounded Vets: Anonymous; Altman, Jack; Amery, Al; Bailey, Thomas; Bowie, John, 1969-1971 (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade (VALB) Questionnaire for Wounded Vets: Cannon, Karl; Colodny, Robert; de Maio, Anthony; Felson, Milton, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade (VALB) Questionnaire for Wounded Vets: Graeber, Kenneth; Groden, Daniel; Harris, Aaron; Hall, Harvey, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade (VALB) Questionnaire for Wounded Vets: Jordan, Frank; Kane, Larry; Keller, Fred; Koblick, John, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade (VALB) Questionnaire for Wounded Vets: Lockett, John; Lossowski, Vincent; MacLeod, Dan; Pacey, Donald, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 49)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade (VALB) Questionnaire for Wounded Vets: Perlman, Norman; Ross, Adolph; Siegel, Joseph; Sims, John, 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 50)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade (VALB) Questionnaire for Wounded Vets: Smith, Randall; Stamm, Morris; Yale, Stuart; Tivin, Isadore, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 51)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade (VALB) Questionnaire for Wounded Vets: Toney, Anthony; Valuch, Rudolph; Van der Schelling, Bart; Wesson, Neil, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 52)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade (VALB) Questionnaire for Wounded Vets: Wheeler, Bill; Wolff, Milton; Yellin, Jack; Ziedman, Frank, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 53)
  - Zell, Rosa Hilda: Poetry and Notes (Box 29, Folder 54)
- Series VI: Artifacts: Textiles and Pin, 1937
  Series VI. Artifacts: Textiles and Pin, ca. 1937. There are two items in this series: The black wool nurse's cape Martin wore in Spain, and a Medical Bureau pin - a gold cross surrounded by laurel leaves.
  - Spanish Civil War Nurse's Cape, 1937 (Box 30, Item 1)
  - Spanish Civil War Nurse's Pin, 1937 (Box 30, Item 2)
- Series VII: Duplicates, 1936-1984
  Series VII. Duplicates, 1936-1984. When archivists at Brandeis University initially inventoried the Fredericka Martin collection in 1991, five boxes of duplicate material (chiefly carbons and photocopies) were separated and retained. These boxes, which were transferred to New York University in January 2001, are shelved with the processed manuscript materials in Boxes 32-36; they are available for review upon request.
  - Duplicates, 1936-1984 (Box 31)
  - Duplicates, 1936-1984 (Box 32)
  - Duplicates, 1936-1984 (Box 33)
  - Duplicates, 1936-1984 (Box 34)
  - Duplicates, 1936-1984 (Box 35)
- Series IX. 2015 Accretion
  Arrangement
  This series has not been arranged by an archivist. The materials are arranged in the order in which they were received from the donor.
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists almost entirely of correspondence from the 1970s and 1980s to and from Martin regarding her research on the Abraham Lincoln Brigade and the nurses and medical personnel in the Medical Bureau and North American Committee to Aid Spanish Democracy. The series also includes a small number of photographs, some of which appear to date from the 1930s in Spain during the Spanish Civil War. Explanatory notes attached to various documents, groups of documents and folders were written by Tobyanne Berenberg, Martin's daughter.
  - Photographs, 1954 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Framed Photographs, undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Materials on Other Veterans, 1960-1979 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence with Theodore (Ted) Ryberg, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 4-7)
  - Mollie Steimer and Semo Flechine, 1969-1981 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Doris Hayden, 1959-1969 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Wayne State University Group, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Mary Cunningham, 1970 September 15 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Charlotte Abbott, 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Alice Wexler, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Stacy Phillips, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Jane Wholey, 1977-1981 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Hill and Wang, 1960-1984 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence, 1938-1989 (Box 40, Folder 17-22)
  - Moe Fishman Correspondence with Tobyanne Berenberg, 1971-1995 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence and Clippings, 1964-2014 (Box 40, Folder 24-25)
- Series X. 2020 Accretion, 1930-2019; 1.5 Linear Feet in 2 manuscript boxes and 2 half manuscript boxes
  This accretion to the Fredericka Martin Papers consists of materials created and collected by Martin and her daughter TobyAnne Berenberg documenting Martin's experiences as a nurse in the Spanish Civil War, her life in Mexico, and her career as a writer. Materials include personal correspondence, diaries, biographical information about Martin, newspaper clippings on subjects of interest to Martin, and published writings. Many folders in this accretion contain an explanatory note by Berenberg describing the materials' significance in the context of Martin's life.
  - Aleut Language, 1946 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Articles by Martin in The American Indian, 1946, 1950 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Biographical Information, 1930-2019 (Box 41, Box 2-8, Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Citizenship and Residency Controversies, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Courses Taught at Centro Intercultural de Documentacion (CIDOC), 1968-1976 (Box 41, Folder 10-11)
  - Crown Publishers -- Guide to Mexico, 1963-1970 (Box 41, Folder 12, Box 42, Folder 1-2)
  - Diary, 1941 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Diary, 1956 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Economic Assistance, 1977, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Greenbelt, Maryland, 1939-1984 (Box 44, Folder 3-4)
  - How to Live And/Or Work in Mexico Typescript, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 6-8)
  - Immigration Documents for Mexico, 1954-1961 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Personal Correspondence -- General, 1967-1988 (Box 43, Folder 1-2)
  - Personal Correspondence -- Ben Berenberg, 1961-1981 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Personal Correspondence -- Family, 1974-1981 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Personal Correspondence -- Paul Nelson, 1943-1946 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Personal Correspondence -- The Silver Fleece, 1974-1981 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Personal Correspondence -- Margaret Shedd, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Research Trip on American Medical Bureau in Spanish Civil War, 1972-1974 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Spanish Civil War, 1946-1982 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - "Spanish Diary," James Neugass, 1938 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Spanish Newspaper Clippings, 2019 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - United American Spanish Aid Committee, American Rescue Ship Mission, 1940 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - University of Alaska-Fairbanks Library, circa 1972 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Series XI. 2021 Accretion, 1947-1984; .25 Linear Feet in 2 folders
  This accretion to the Fredericka Martin Papers consists of correspondence concerning the Crumhorn property, as well as correspondence, newsletters, and ephemera documenting Martin's membership in the Society of Woman Geographers.
  - Crumhorn Property, 1983-1984 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Society of Woman Geographers, 1947-1972 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Series XII. 2024 Accretion, 1923-1988; 2.04 Linear Feet in 2 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, 1 media box, and 1 folder in shared housing; 25 audiocassettes
  This accretion to the Fredericka Martin Papers consists of materials created and collected by Martin and her daughter TobyAnne Berengberg documenting Martin's experiences as a nurse in the Spanish Civil War, her life in Mexico, and her career as a writer. Materials in this accretion include correspondence; biographical files that Martin kept about herself inclusive of notes, family research, journal entries, curated and contextualized clippings; and original writings by Martin, inclusive of poetry, drafts of novels, a copy of Martin's text on speaking Mexican Spanish (with accompanying documentation about the texts' publication and reception), and notes about Martin's writing practice. This series also includes audio recordings of interviews by Martin on the Spanish Civil War.
  Appraisal
  Appraised out of this accretion of material are clippings and family administrative documents including copies of marriage licenses, death certificates, and a passport.
  - Poems, 1939-1951, undated (Box 45, Folder 1-3)
  - Poems and Other Writings, 1938-1968 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - No Other Way (Novel), undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Untitled Novel Manuscript (Labelled "Golden Arrow -- Remedio Theme"), undated (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Everyday Mexican Spanish -- Published Copy, 1958 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Everyday Mexican Spanish -- Reviews, Correspondence, 1958-1981 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Everyday Mexican Spanish -- Notes, Correspondence, 1958-1960 (Box 45, Folder 9-10)
  - Publishers Correspondence, 1944-1946 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Notes on Writing Process and Schedule, undated (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Book Reviews and Royalties, 1960-1984 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - CIDOC / Van Illich Editing, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence -- Isidore Bassoff "Kelly", 1951-1987 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence -- Sam Peck, 1950-1951 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence -- Alex Cohen, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence -- Tobyanne Berenberg, 1941-1948 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence -- Samuel Berenberg, Alexander Calder, 1944-1947 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence -- Rosa Hilda Zell, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence -- Whitford Carter, 1964-1967 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence -- Daisy Taylor, 1944-1947 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence -- Rush Harp, 1974-1982 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence -- Paul Nelson, 1945-1946 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence -- Lini De Vries, 1958-1959 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence -- General, 1939-1983 (Box 47, Folder 12-14)
  - Journal Entries, 1939-1954 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Biographical Notes, 1932-1985 (Box 47, Folder 16-19, Folder 1-2)
  - Biographical Materials -- CV and Education, 1923-1979 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Biographical Materials -- Relationship with Alex Cohen, 1948-1985 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Ambulance Unit 1, 1937 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Society of Friends of the Museum of Cuauhnahuac, undated (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Frances Patai, 1989-1993 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Ephemera, undated (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Professional Associations, 1939-1968 (Box 47, Folder 9-10)
  - HUAC, 1964-1972 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence with Dr. Samuel Righter Berenberg (Husband), 1939-1952 (Box 48, Folder 1-10)
  - Biographical Materials, 1935-1974 (Box 48, Folder 11-25)
  - Writings, 1938-1968 (Box 49, Folder 1-19)
  - Correspondence, Photographs, Notes, and Ephemera, 1937-1984 (Box 49, Folder 20-31, Box 50, Folder 1-3)
  - Personal Documents, 1937-1973 (Box 50, Folder 4-5)
  - Journals and Writings, 1946-1960 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Medical Bureau Armband, circa late 1930s (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Christ Hospital Nurses Cap (Spain), circa late 1930s (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - The Fight for Peace and Democracy, 1938 (Box Shared Tamiment 164, Folder 21)
  - Interviews by Fredericka Martin about the Spanish Civil War, 1966-1986
    - Audio Recording, 1966-1986 (Box 51, Audiocassette 001.0001)
    - Audio Recording, 1966-1986 (Box 51, Audiocassette 001.0002)
    - Audio Recording, 1966-1986 (Box 51, Audiocassette 001.0003)
    - Audio Recording, 1966-1986 (Box 51, Audiocassette 001.0004)
    - Audio Recording, 1966-1986 (Box 51, Audiocassette 001.0005)
    - Audio Recording, 1966-1986 (Box 51, Audiocassette 001.0006)
    - Audio Recording, 1966-1986 (Box 51, Audiocassette 001.0007)
    - Audio Recording, 1966-1986 (Box 51, Audiocassette 001.0008)
    - Audio Recording, 1966-1986 (Box 51, Audiocassette 001.0009)
    - Audio Recording, 1966-1986 (Box 51, Audiocassette 001.0010)
    - Audio Recording, 1966-1986 (Box 51, Audiocassette 001.0011)
    - Audio Recording, 1966-1986 (Box 51, Audiocassette 001.0012)
    - Audio Recording, 1966-1986 (Box 51, Audiocassette 001.0013)
    - Audio Recording, 1966-1986 (Box 51, Audiocassette 001.0014)
    - Audio Recording, 1966-1986 (Box 51, Audiocassette 001.0015)
    - Audio Recording, 1966-1986 (Box 51, Audiocassette 001.0016)
    - Audio Recording, 1966-1986 (Box 51, Audiocassette 001.0017)
    - Audio Recording, 1966-1986 (Box 51, Audiocassette 001.0018)
    - Audio Recording, 1966-1986 (Box 51, Audiocassette 001.0019)
    - Audio Recording, 1966-1986 (Box 51, Audiocassette 001.0020)
    - Audio Recording, 1966-1986 (Box 51, Audiocassette 001.0021)
    - Audio Recording, 1966-1986 (Box 51, Audiocassette 001.0022)
    - Audio Recording, 1966-1986 (Box 51, Audiocassette 001.0023)
    - Audio Recording, 1966-1986 (Box 51, Audiocassette 001.0024)
    - Audio Recording, 1966-1986 (Box 51, Audiocassette 001.0025)